Bob Bullock Comptroller of Public Accounts papers, Inclusive: 1970-1991, Bulk: 1975-1990
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
- Correspondence, 1975-1990; 1
  - General, 1975-1990; 1
    - 1987, 2
      - Fox, Louis J., 1987 (Box 69, Folder 34)
      - Frost, Martin, 1987 (Box 69, Folder 35)
      - Galloway, Gale L., 1987 (Box 69, Folder 36)
      - Gangi, Frank J., 1987 (Box 69, Folder 37)
      - Garcia, Frank J., 1987 (Box 69, Folder 38)
      - Garcia, Orlando L., 1987 (Box 69, Folder 39)
      - Garland, George T. Jr., 1987 (Box 69, Folder 40)
      - Gaskin, L.A., 1987 (Box 69, Folder 41)
      - Gauss, Phillip, 1987 (Box 69, Folder 42)
      - Gaut, C. Rufus, 1987 (Box 69, Folder 43)
      - Geistweidt, Gerald, 1987 (Box 69, Folder 44)
      - Gentry, C.H., 1987 (Box 69, Folder 45)
      - George, Dickie, 1987 (Box 69, Folder 46)
      - Gephardt, Richard, 1987 (Box 69, Folder 47)
      - Gillig, Walter C. Jr., 1987 (Box 69, Folder 48)
      - Glasgow, Robert J., 1987 (Box 69, Folder 49)
      - Gold, Steven D., 1987 (Box 70, Folder 1)
      - Goldstein, Louis L., 1987 (Box 70, Folder 2)
      - Golman, George H., 1987 (Box 70, Folder 3)
      - Gondek, George J., 1987 (Box 70, Folder 4)
      - Gonzalez, Henry B., 1987 (Box 70, Folder 5)
      - Gramm, Phil, 1987 (Box 70, Folder 6)
      - Graves, Gordon, 1987 (Box 70, Folder 7)
      - Gray, Jack, 1987 (Box 70, Folder 8)
      - Green, Gene, 1987 (Box 70, Folder 9)
      - Green, Roy W., 1987 (Box 70, Folder 10)
      - Green, Tom, 1987 (Box 70, Folder 11)
      - Griffin, Holman M., 1987 (Box 70, Folder 12)
      - Grimes, Gary, 1987 (Box 70, Folder 13)
      - Grossman, Hyman, 1987 (Box 70, Folder 14)
      - Grozier, Conrad, 1987 (Box 70, Folder 15)
      - Guerrero, Lena, 1987 (Box 70, Folder 16)
      - Gullahorn, Jack W., 1987 (Box 70, Folder 17)
      - Haggard, Eunice, 1987 (Box 70, Folder 18)
      - Hall, E. Wayne, 1987 (Box 70, Folder 19)
      - Hall, Gordon, 1987 (Box 70, Folder 20)
      - Hall, Mimi, 1987 (Box 70, Folder 21)
      - Hall, Walter G. Sr., 1987 (Box 70, Folder 22)
      - Hallam, Robert, 1987 (Box 70, Folder 23)
      - Haltom, JoNell, 1987 (Box 70, Folder 24)
      - Hammock, Clifford, 1987 (Box 70, Folder 25)
      - Hanna, Debbie, 1987 (Box 70, Folder 26)
      - Hardy, James S., 1987 (Box 70, Folder 27)
      - Harris, Chris, 1987 (Box 70, Folder 28)
      - Harris, O.H., 1987 (Box 70, Folder 29)
      - Harrison, John Ray, 1987 (Box 70, Folder 30)
      - Hassner, Martin I., 1987 (Box 70, Folder 31)
      - Hawkins, Jack R., 1987 (Box 70, Folder 32)
      - Hay, Jess Thomas, 1987 (Box 70, Folder 33)
      - Haynes, J.J., 1987 (Box 70, Folder 34)
      - Haywood, Tom, 1987 (Box 70, Folder 35)
      - Hazleton, Jared E., 1987 (Box 70, Folder 36)
      - Head, Hayden W. Jr., 1987 (Box 70, Folder 37)
      - Head, Hayden W. Sr., 1987 (Box 70, Folder 38)
      - Hemphill, Wanda, 1987 (Box 70, Folder 39)
      - Herbert, Harvey, 1987 (Box 70, Folder 40)
      - Herriage, Bobby G., 1987 (Box 70, Folder 41)
      - Hershey, Jacob W., 1987 (Box 70, Folder 42)
      - Herskowitz, Robin, 1987 (Box 70, Folder 43)
      - Hibbs, J. Elliott, 1987 (Box 70, Folder 44)
      - Hicks, Norman L., 1987 (Box 70, Folder 45)
      - Hightower, Jim, 1987 (Box 70, Folder 46)
      - Hilbert, Paul J., 1987 (Box 70, Folder 47)
      - Hill, Patricia A., 1987 (Box 70, Folder 48)
      - Hillman, G. Robert, 1987 (Box 70, Folder 49)
      - Hobby, William P. (1 of 3), 1987 (Box 71, Folder 1)
      - Hobby, William P. (2 of 3), 1987 (Box 71, Folder 2)
      - Hobby, William P. (3 of 3), 1987 (Box 71, Folder 3)
      - Hodgin, Robert, 1987 (Box 71, Folder 4)
      - Holland, Charles D., 1987 (Box 71, Folder 5)
      - Hollowman, Tim, 1987 (Box 71, Folder 6)
      - Holloway, Lowell Jr., 1987 (Box 71, Folder 7)
      - Hollowell, Bill, 1987 (Box 71, Folder 8)
      - Holmes, Roy J., 1987 (Box 71, Folder 9)
      - Holt, David Earl, 1987 (Box 71, Folder 10)
      - Holton, Rexford Gwen, 1987 (Box 71, Folder 11)
      - Holzheauser, Steve, 1987 (Box 71, Folder 12)
      - Hood, Hal, 1987 (Box 71, Folder 13)
      - Hopkins, Michael H., 1987 (Box 71, Folder 14)
      - Horany, Jimmy P., 1987 (Box 71, Folder 15)
      - Houston, Rayburn, 1987 (Box 71, Folder 16)
      - Howell, William R., 1987 (Box 71, Folder 17)
      - Hudson, David W., 1987 (Box 71, Folder 18)
      - Hudson, Rod, 1987 (Box 71, Folder 19)
      - Huggins, Joe O., 1987 (Box 71, Folder 20)
      - Hughes, Robert H., 1987 (Box 71, Folder 21)
      - Hull, Don, 1987 (Box 71, Folder 22)
      - Humphrey, John A., 1987 (Box 71, Folder 23)
      - Hunter, Sam, 1987 (Box 71, Folder 24)
      - Hurst, O. Ray, 1987 (Box 71, Folder 25)
      - Irvin, Ross N., 1987 (Box 71, Folder 26)
      - Ivins, Molly, 1987 (Box 71, Folder 27)
      - Jackson, Richie, 1987 (Box 71, Folder 28)
      - James, Thomas N., 1987 (Box 71, Folder 29)
      - Johnson, Cliff, 1987 (Box 71, Folder 30)
      - Johnson, L. Todd, 1987 (Box 71, Folder 31)
      - Johnson, Rob, 1987 (Box 71, Folder 32)
      - Johnson, Sue, 1987 (Box 71, Folder 33)
      - Joiner, Joe M., 1987 (Box 71, Folder 34)
      - Jones, Grant, 1987 (Box 71, Folder 35)
      - Jones, Lee, 1987 (Box 71, Folder 36)
      - Jones, Marcus E., 1987 (Box 71, Folder 37)
      - Joost, David L., 1987 (Box 71, Folder 38)
      - Jordan, De Soto, 1987 (Box 71, Folder 39)
      - Jordan, Robert B., 1987 (Box 71, Folder 40)
      - Justice, Jason, 1987 (Box 71, Folder 41)
      - Kahn, Alan R., 1987 (Box 72, Folder 1)
      - Kane, Stanford L., 1987 (Box 72, Folder 2)
      - Kaster, James J., 1987 (Box 72, Folder 3)
      - Kaus, Thomas, 1987 (Box 72, Folder 4)
      - Kazen, Abaraham Jr., 1987 (Box 72, Folder 5)
      - Keel, John M., 1987 (Box 72, Folder 6)
      - Kelleher, Herbert, 1987 (Box 72, Folder 7)
      - Keller, Mary F., 1987 (Box 72, Folder 8)
      - Keller, Scott, 1987 (Box 72, Folder 9)
      - Kelly, Brian, 1987 (Box 72, Folder 10)
      - Kelly, Don, 1987 (Box 72, Folder 11)
      - Kelly, George W., 1987 (Box 72, Folder 12)
      - Kilgore, Joe M., 1987 (Box 72, Folder 13)
      - Kim, John, 1987 (Box 72, Folder 14)
      - King, Howard A., 1987 (Box 72, Folder 15)
      - King, Thomas S., 1987 (Box 72, Folder 16)
      - Kingston, Mike, 1987 (Box 72, Folder 17)
      - Kins, Sammy, 1987 (Box 72, Folder 18)
      - Kirk, Paul G. Jr., 1987 (Box 72, Folder 19)
      - Knaggs, John R., 1987 (Box 72, Folder 20)
      - Knapp, Charles M., 1987 (Box 72, Folder 21)
      - Knop, Todd, 1987 (Box 72, Folder 22)
      - Korbel, George, 1987 (Box 72, Folder 23)
      - Kralj, Nick, 1987 (Box 72, Folder 24)
      - Kress, Barnett Alexander, 1987 (Box 72, Folder 25)
      - Krier, Cynthia Taylor, 1987 (Box 72, Folder 26)
      - Krute, Susan, 1987 (Box 72, Folder 27)
      - Kubiak, L.B., 1987 (Box 72, Folder 28)
      - Kuby, Karl F., 1987 (Box 72, Folder 29)
      - LaGrone, Troy H., 1987 (Box 72, Folder 30)
      - LaMarche, Gara, 1987 (Box 72, Folder 31)
      - Laney, James E. “Pete”, 1987 (Box 72, Folder 32)
      - Latta, Don, 1987 (Box 72, Folder 33)
      - Lea, Joe E. Jr., 1987 (Box 72, Folder 34)
      - Lebermann, Lowell H. Jr., 1987 (Box 72, Folder 35)
      - Leblanc, R.P. Jr., 1987 (Box 72, Folder 36)
      - Leedom, John N., 1987 (Box 72, Folder 37)
      - Lewis, Gibson D., 1987 (Box 72, Folder 38)
      - Lewis, Ron E., 1987 (Box 72, Folder 39)
      - Ligon, W.H., 1987 (Box 72, Folder 40)
      - Lilie, Walt, 1987 (Box 72, Folder 41)
      - Lisnow, Harmon, 1987 (Box 72, Folder 42)
      - Lockley, Joyce, 1987 (Box 72, Folder 43)
      - Loftis, Jack D., 1987 (Box 72, Folder 44)
      - Logan, John A., 1987 (Box 72, Folder 45)
      - Longoria, Raul L., 1987 (Box 72, Folder 46)
      - Lowry, Margaret, 1987 (Box 72, Folder 47)
      - Lucio, Eduardo A. Jr., 1987 (Box 72, Folder 48)
      - Luna, Albert III, 1987 (Box 72, Folder 49)
      - Lyde, H.K., 1987 (Box 72, Folder 50)
      - Lyon, Ted, 1987 (Box 72, Folder 51)
      - Mabe, Jody, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 1)
      - Macey, Louis, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 2)
      - Madla, Frank Lloyd, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 3)
      - Manges, Clint, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 4)
      - Manges, Dan, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 5)
      - Manges, Ruth, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 6)
      - Manzano, David, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 7)
      - Marchant, Ken, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 8)
      - Mark, Hans, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 9)
      - Martin, James G., 1987 (Box 73, Folder 10)
      - Martin, Julian G., 1987 (Box 73, Folder 11)
      - Martin, Susan Work, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 12)
      - Martinez, Roman, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 13)
      - Mattox, James A. “Jim” (1 of 2), 1987 (Box 73, Folder 14)
      - Mattox, James A. “Jim” (2 of 2), 1987 (Box 73, Folder 15)
      - Mauro, Judith, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 16)
      - Mauzy, Oscar H., 1987 (Box 73, Folder 17)
      - Mayborn, Frank W., 1987 (Box 73, Folder 18)
      - Mazur, Edward J., 1987 (Box 73, Folder 19)
      - McAden, Don, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 20)
      - McAlsiter, E.E. “Moe”, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 21)
      - McBeath, William Sherman, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 22)
      - McBee, Frank W. Jr., 1987 (Box 73, Folder 23)
      - McCabe, Richard E., 1987 (Box 73, Folder 24)
      - McCalla, Clay, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 25)
      - McDonald, Carol L., 1987 (Box 73, Folder 26)
      - McDonald, Nancy, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 27)
      - McFarland, Bob, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 28)
      - McGee, Cleo Cobb, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 29)
      - McGee, William H., 1987 (Box 73, Folder 30)
      - McKnight, Felix, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 31)
      - McGuinn, David P., 1987 (Box 73, Folder 32)
      - McGuffin, David A., 1987 (Box 73, Folder 33)
      - McKensie, Barbara, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 34)
      - McKie, James W., 1987 (Box 73, Folder 35)
      - McKinney, Michael, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 36)
      - McKnight, William M. Jr., 1987 (Box 73, Folder 37)
      - McLane, John Bonner, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 38)
      - McMillan, Tom F., 1987 (Box 73, Folder 39)
      - McWilliams, Jim, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 40)
      - Mecham, Evan, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 41)
      - Mellard, Joan, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 42)
      - Mellard, Robert, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 43)
      - Melton, Bob, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 44)
      - Merkens, Guido A., 1987 (Box 73, Folder 45)
      - Messer, Bill, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 46)
      - Meyer, Ralph, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 47)
      - Meyers, James R., 1987 (Box 73, Folder 48)
      - Mills, R. Coke, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 49)
      - Minton, David, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 50)
      - Minton, Roy Q., 1987 (Box 73, Folder 51)
      - Mischer, Walter M. Sr., 1987 (Box 73, Folder 52)
      - Mobley, Mary K., 1987 (Box 74, Folder 1)
      - Mogil, Leonard, 1987 (Box 74, Folder 2)
      - Monroe, Marilyn, 1987 (Box 74, Folder 3)
      - Montalvo, Ramon, 1987 (Box 74, Folder 4)
      - Montford, John T., 1987 (Box 74, Folder 5)
      - Montgomery, Larry K., 1987 (Box 74, Folder 6)
      - Moore, Lucille N., 1987 (Box 74, Folder 7)
      - Moravits, George, 1987 (Box 74, Folder 8)
      - Morales, Daniel C., 1987 (Box 74, Folder 9)
      - Moreno, Alejandro Jr., 1987 (Box 74, Folder 10)
      - Moreno, Paul C., 1987 (Box 74, Folder 11)
      - Muller, Mary Bernadette, 1987 (Box 74, Folder 12)
      - Mountz, Thomas W., 1987 (Box 74, Folder 13)
      - Murphey, Thomas O., 1987 (Box 74, Folder 14)
      - Murphree, Roger W., 1987 (Box 74, Folder 15)
      - Nabers, Lynn, 1987 (Box 74, Folder 16)
      - Neill, Dian K., 1987 (Box 74, Folder 17)
      - Neil, W.R. “Bill”, 1987 (Box 74, Folder 18)
      - Newman, Gwen, 1987 (Box 74, Folder 19)
      - Nichols, John F., 1987 (Box 74, Folder 20)
      - Noel, William D., 1987 (Box 74, Folder 21)
      - Nugent, James E., 1987 (Box 74, Folder 22)
      - Odam, John W., 1987 (Box 74, Folder 23)
      - Oliphint, Albert William II, 1987 (Box 74, Folder 24)
      - Oliver, James P., 1987 (Box 74, Folder 25)
      - Olsen, Lawrence, 1987 (Box 74, Folder 26)
      - Olson, Lyndon L., 1987 (Box 74, Folder 27)
      - O’Malley, Dennis S., 1987 (Box 74, Folder 28)
      - O’Neal, Patricia J., 1987 (Box 74, Folder 29)
      - Orton, Richard, 1987 (Box 74, Folder 30)
      - Osadchey, Rabbi Shaul, 1987 (Box 74, Folder 31)
      - Oxford, Hubert III, 1987 (Box 74, Folder 32)
      - Padilla, R.O., 1987 (Box 74, Folder 33)
      - Paine, William B., 1987 (Box 74, Folder 34)
      - Parker, Carl A., 1987 (Box 74, Folder 35)
      - Parmer, Hugh, 1987 (Box 74, Folder 36)
      - Passions, Donna J., 1987 (Box 74, Folder 37)
      - Patterson, Edith, 1987 (Box 74, Folder 38)
      - Patterson, L.P., 1987 (Box 74, Folder 39)
      - Pavlu, Joe, 1987 (Box 74, Folder 40)
      - Perot, H. Ross, 1987 (Box 74, Folder 41)
      - Perry, Rick, 1987 (Box 74, Folder 42)
      - Peter, R.L., 1987 (Box 74, Folder 43)
      - Pfeiffer, Elsie B., 1987 (Box 74, Folder 44)
      - Phinney, R.L., 1987 (Box 74, Folder 45)
      - Pickens, Thomas Boone Jr., 1987 (Box 74, Folder 46)
      - Pickle, J.J., 1987 (Box 74, Folder 47)
      - Pierce, George, 1987 (Box 74, Folder 48)
      - Pinckney, Thomas D., 1987 (Box 74, Folder 49)
      - Pitcock, Doug, 1987 (Box 74, Folder 50)
      - Pitts, Shelby D., 1987 (Box 74, Folder 51)
      - Pollard, Joyce, 1987 (Box 74, Folder 52)
      - Polumbo, Anthony L., 1987 (Box 74, Folder 53)
      - Powers, William C. Jr., 1987 (Box 74, Folder 54)
      - Presnal, James K., 1987 (Box 74, Folder 55)
      - Price, W.H., 1987 (Box 74, Folder 56)
      - Rains, Jack M., 1987 (Box 75, Folder 1)
      - Rangel, Irma, 1987 (Box 75, Folder 2)
      - Rankin, Joe, 1987 (Box 75, Folder 3)
      - Rapoport, Bernard, 1987 (Box 75, Folder 4)
      - Ratcliff, Ben F., 1987 (Box 75, Folder 5)
      - Ratcuff, Joseph, 1987 (Box 75, Folder 6)
      - Ray, Donald W., 1987 (Box 75, Folder 7)
      - Rayborn, Ralph, 1987 (Box 75, Folder 8)
      - Reagan, Harold E., 1987 (Box 75, Folder 9)
      - Reeb, Charles L., 1987 (Box 75, Folder 10)
      - Reiswerg, Meyer, 1987 (Box 75, Folder 11)
      - Reyckert, Donna E., 1987 (Box 75, Folder 12)
      - Rice, Karol, 1987 (Box 75, Folder 13)
      - Richards, Ann W. (1 of 2), 1987 (Box 75, Folder 14)
      - Richards, Ann W. (2 of 2), 1987 (Box 75, Folder 15)
      - Richards, Cecile, 1987 (Box 75, Folder 16)
      - Richardson, Bob, 1987 (Box 75, Folder 17)
      - Richter, Walter H., 1987 (Box 75, Folder 18)
      - Riley, Randall, 1987 (Box 75, Folder 19)
      - Rives, Laura, 1987 (Box 75, Folder 20)
      - Roberts, Wesley B., 1987 (Box 75, Folder 21)
      - Robbins, Eugene W., 1987 (Box 75, Folder 22)
      - Robertson, Sam L. Jr., 1987 (Box 75, Folder 23)
      - Robinson, Jerry L., 1987 (Box 75, Folder 24)
      - Roden, Tom, 1987 (Box 75, Folder 25)
      - Rodriquez, Mary Helen, 1987 (Box 75, Folder 26)
      - Rogers, Mary Beth, 1987 (Box 75, Folder 27)
      - Rose, Howard V., 1987 (Box 75, Folder 28)
      - Rose, Jim R., 1987 (Box 75, Folder 29)
      - Roye, W. Payne, 1987 (Box 75, Folder 30)
      - Rudd, Jim D., 1987 (Box 75, Folder 31)
      - Ruiz, J. Edgar, 1987 (Box 75, Folder 32)
      - Ruiz, Olivia B., 1987 (Box 75, Folder 33)
      - Ryan, Paul, 1987 (Box 75, Folder 34)
      - Salinas, Homar, 1987 (Box 75, Folder 35)
      - Sallop, Marvin B., 1987 (Box 75, Folder 36)
      - Sanchez, Manuel A., 1987 (Box 75, Folder 37)
      - Sapp, David R., 1987 (Box 75, Folder 38)
      - Sarpalius, Bill, 1987 (Box 75, Folder 39)
      - Saunders, Robert M., 1987 (Box 75, Folder 40)
      - Schlett, Mary L., 1987 (Box 75, Folder 41)
      - Schlueter, Stan, 1987 (Box 75, Folder 42)
      - Schreiner, Charles III, 1987 (Box 75, Folder 43)
      - Scofield, Frank E., 1987 (Box 75, Folder 44)
      - Scott, Morin M., 1987 (Box 75, Folder 45)
      - Scott, Stanley, 1987 (Box 75, Folder 46)
      - Seidlits, Curtis L. Jr., 1987 (Box 75, Folder 47)
      - Senter, Sandy, 1987 (Box 75, Folder 48)
      - Sessions, John, 1987 (Box 75, Folder 49)
      - Shaprio, Sander W., 1987 (Box 76, Folder 1)
      - Sharp, John S., 1987 (Box 76, Folder 2)
      - Shaver, Mr. & Mrs. Bob, 1987 (Box 76, Folder 3)
      - Shaw, Larry Don, 1987 (Box 76, Folder 4)
      - Shaw, Nancy, 1987 (Box 76, Folder 5)
      - Shear, Mr. & Mrs. James, 1987 (Box 76, Folder 6)
      - Sheffield, Susanna, 1987 (Box 76, Folder 7)
      - Sheppard, John Ben, 1987 (Box 76, Folder 8)
      - Shine, Hugh D., 1987 (Box 76, Folder 9)
      - Shipley, George C., 1987 (Box 76, Folder 10)
      - Short, Alex H., 1987 (Box 76, Folder 11)
      - Simpson, Harold B., 1987 (Box 76, Folder 12)
      - Sims, Bill, 1987 (Box 76, Folder 13)
      - Sitton, Alice, 1987 (Box 76, Folder 14)
      - Sloan, C.R., 1987 (Box 76, Folder 15)
      - Small, Clint C., 1987 (Box 76, Folder 16)
      - Smith, James Patrick, 1987 (Box 76, Folder 17)
      - Smith, L.G. “Skip”, 1987 (Box 76, Folder 18)
      - Smith, Richard A., 1987 (Box 76, Folder 19)
      - Smothers, Patricia J., 1987 (Box 76, Folder 20)
      - Snow, Toney, 1987 (Box 76, Folder 21)
      - Sparks, Robert H. “Butch”, 1987 (Box 76, Folder 22)
      - Spurgers, Willie P., 1987 (Box 76, Folder 23)
      - Steen, Lias B. “Bubba”, 1987 (Box 76, Folder 24)
      - Stephens, Jerry D., 1987 (Box 76, Folder 25)
      - Stewart, Robert H. III, 1987 (Box 76, Folder 26)
      - Stiles, Mark, 1987 (Box 76, Folder 27)
      - Stoudt, William K., 1987 (Box 76, Folder 28)
      - Strauss, Richard C., 1987 (Box 76, Folder 29)
      - Streim, Hannes, 1987 (Box 76, Folder 30)
      - Stubblefield, Cecil H., 1987 (Box 76, Folder 31)
      - Stumberg, Louis H., 1987 (Box 76, Folder 32)
      - Sullivan, Mike, 1987 (Box 76, Folder 33)
      - Sullivant, Larry B., 1987 (Box 76, Folder 34)
      - Sussman, Barry, 1987 (Box 76, Folder 35)
      - Sutton, Lou Nelle, 1987 (Box 76, Folder 36)
      - Swartz, Thomas J., 1987 (Box 76, Folder 37)
      - Sweeney, Mac, 1987 (Box 76, Folder 38)
      - Tallas, James L., 1987 (Box 77, Folder 1)
      - Tarbox, Max R., 1987 (Box 77, Folder 2)
      - Taub, Henry J.N., 1987 (Box 77, Folder 3)
      - Taylor, M.A., 1987 (Box 77, Folder 4)
      - Teaver, Larry, 1987 (Box 77, Folder 5)
      - Teggeman, Erwin, 1987 (Box 77, Folder 6)
      - Tejeda, Frank M., 1987 (Box 77, Folder 7)
      - Templer, William B., 1987 (Box 77, Folder 8)
      - Terrell, Charles T., 1987 (Box 77, Folder 9)
      - Thompson, A. Leon Jr., 1987 (Box 77, Folder 10)
      - Timmins, J.Y., 1987 (Box 77, Folder 11)
      - Tindell, Stan, 1987 (Box 77, Folder 12)
      - Townsend, Tommy, 1987 (Box 77, Folder 13)
      - Travis, Charles D., 1987 (Box 77, Folder 14)
      - Traeger, John A., 1987 (Box 77, Folder 15)
      - Triplett, Tom, 1987 (Box 77, Folder 16)
      - Trotti, Robert S., 1987 (Box 77, Folder 17)
      - Truan, Carlos F., 1987 (Box 77, Folder 18)
      - True, S.M. Jr., 1987 (Box 77, Folder 19)
      - Tucker, Jake T., 1987 (Box 77, Folder 20)
      - Turnbull, Elliott B. III, 1987 (Box 77, Folder 21)
      - Turner, Russ, 1987 (Box 77, Folder 22)
      - Uher, Donald R., 1987 (Box 77, Folder 23)
      - Urbie, Hector R., 1987 (Box 77, Folder 24)
      - Vasquez, John, 1987 (Box 77, Folder 25)
      - Vogt, George W., 1987 (Box 77, Folder 26)
      - Vowell, Jack C. Jr., 1987 (Box 77, Folder 27)
      - Wade, C.P. Jr., 1987 (Box 77, Folder 28)
      - Waldrep, Kent, 1987 (Box 77, Folder 29)
      - Waldrop, Tom, 1987 (Box 77, Folder 30)
      - Walker, George H., 1987 (Box 77, Folder 31)
      - Walker, Odell M., 1987 (Box 77, Folder 32)
      - Walker, Thomas W. Jr., 1987 (Box 77, Folder 33)
      - Wallace, Mack, 1987 (Box 77, Folder 34)
      - Wallace, Ralph R., 1987 (Box 77, Folder 35)
      - Walsh, Richard J., 1987 (Box 77, Folder 36)
      - Ward, Phil, 1987 (Box 77, Folder 37)
      - Ward, Travis, 1987 (Box 77, Folder 38)
      - Warner, Philip G., 1987 (Box 77, Folder 39)
      - Watson, John E., 1987 (Box 78, Folder 1)
      - Watson, Murray, 1987 (Box 78, Folder 2)
      - Wayne, Ralph, 1987 (Box 78, Folder 3)
      - Webb, C.W., 1987 (Box 78, Folder 4)
      - Welch, Jack, 1987 (Box 78, Folder 5)
      - Wellborn, Jodi, 1987 (Box 78, Folder 6)
      - Wessels, James A., 1987 (Box 78, Folder 7)
      - Westbrook, Pat D., 1987 (Box 78, Folder 8)
      - Weyel, Foster L., 1987 (Box 78, Folder 9)
      - Whaley, J. Foster, 1987 (Box 78, Folder 10)
      - Wheat, Josiah, 1987 (Box 78, Folder 11)
      - Wilkins, Clay A., 1987 (Box 78, Folder 12)
      - Williams, Bob D., 1987 (Box 78, Folder 13)
      - Williams, E.W., 1987 (Box 78, Folder 14)
      - Williams, Kenneth G., 1987 (Box 78, Folder 15)
      - Williams, Lyndell, 1987 (Box 78, Folder 16)
      - Williamson, Richard F., 1987 (Box 78, Folder 17)
      - Williford, Edward A., 1987 (Box 78, Folder 18)
      - Willis, Doyle, 1987 (Box 78, Folder 19)
      - Willis, Robert C., 1987 (Box 78, Folder 20)
      - Wilson, Eddie, 1987 (Box 78, Folder 21)
      - Wing, John, 1987 (Box 78, Folder 22)
      - Winn, Gerald L., 1987 (Box 78, Folder 23)
      - Wise, Watson, W., 1987 (Box 78, Folder 24)
      - Witts, David A., 1987 (Box 78, Folder 25)
      - Wolens, Steven D., 1987 (Box 78, Folder 26)
      - Womack, Drew, 1987 (Box 78, Folder 27)
      - Wood, Bill, 1987 (Box 78, Folder 28)
      - Wood, Gary E., 1987 (Box 78, Folder 29)
      - Woodka, Raymond A., 1987 (Box 78, Folder 30)
      - Woods, Joe M., 1987 (Box 78, Folder 31)
      - Woytec, David G., 1987 (Box 78, Folder 32)
      - Wright, Gary, 1987 (Box 78, Folder 33)
      - Wright, Jim, 1987 (Box 78, Folder 34)
      - Wright, Larry C., 1987 (Box 78, Folder 35)
      - Wright, Linus, 1987 (Box 78, Folder 36)
      - Wyatt, Oscar S. Jr., 1987 (Box 78, Folder 37)
      - Yarborough, Ralph W., 1987 (Box 78, Folder 38)
      - Yi, Frank, 1987 (Box 78, Folder 39)
      - Yost, Gerald V., 1987 (Box 78, Folder 40)
      - Young, Samuel D. Jr., 1987 (Box 78, Folder 41)
      - Young, Thomas, 1987 (Box 78, Folder 42)
      - Zimmerer, Ann M., 1987 (Box 78, Folder 43)
      - Zivley, Lane, 1987 (Box 78, Folder 44)
    - 1988-1989, 3
      - Abington, Bill, 1988 (Box 79, Folder 1)
      - Adair, Paul N., 1988 (Box 79, Folder 2)
      - Adams, Don, 1988 (Box 79, Folder 3)
      - Adrian, Curtis B., 1988 (Box 79, Folder 4)
      - Andridge, Peggy (1 of 2), 1988 (Box 79, Folder 5)
      - Aldridge, Peggy (2 of 2), 1988 (Box 79, Folder 6)
      - Aleshire, William, 1988 (Box 79, Folder 7)
      - Alexander, Thomas P., 1988 (Box 79, Folder 8)
      - Allaway, William H. Jr., 1988 (Box 79, Folder 9)
      - Allen, Kenneth J., 1988 (Box 79, Folder 10)
      - Almon, Jan N., 1988 (Box 79, Folder 11)
      - Altgelt, Woodward W. Jr., 1988 (Box 79, Folder 12)
      - Alwin, Lawrence F., 1988 (Box 79, Folder 13)
      - Anaya, Carmen, 1988 (Box 79, Folder 14)
      - Anaya, Eddie, 1988 (Box 79, Folder 15)
      - Anderson, Andy, 1988 (Box 79, Folder 16)
      - Andrews, Michael A., 1988 (Box 79, Folder 17)
      - Aranda, Juan Jr., 1988 (Box 79, Folder 18)
      - Archer, Bill, 1988 (Box 79, Folder 19)
      - Archer, James E. Jr., 1988 (Box 79, Folder 20)
      - Aresty, Maruice J., 1988 (Box 79, Folder 21)
      - Armas, Jose, 1988 (Box 79, Folder 22)
      - Armendariz, Nora, 1988 (Box 79, Folder 23)
      - Armey, Richard, 1988 (Box 79, Folder 24)
      - Armstrong, J. Gaylord, 1988 (Box 79, Folder 25)
      - Armstrong, John B., 1988 (Box 79, Folder 26)
      - Atchley, James R., 1988 (Box 79, Folder 27)
      - Austin, T. Louis Jr., 1988 (Box 79, Folder 28)
      - Avrett, Bill T., 1988 (Box 79, Folder 29)
      - Ayers, Ross, 1988 (Box 79, Folder 30)
      - Bagsby, Dionne, 1988 (Box 79, Folder 31)
      - Bailey, Charles W. “Bill”, 1988 (Box 79, Folder 32)
      - Bailey, Joe M., 1988 (Box 79, Folder 33)
      - Bailey, Ken, 1988 (Box 79, Folder 34)
      - Baker, Colbert “Bud”, 1988 (Box 79, Folder 35)